[Praise]
No, you don't understand, I am saying that the
security at the airport is very
tight, Mashaallah. On the other hand, in the
name of security in the railways, they are
pretending and let me tell you about this hypocrisy.
My personal thought is that this pretense has to be fulfilled always so that the other person feels
hi, understand this meaning,
like the guys do
in relationships, that girls think this is my
night and shining arm, this is my arm, this is my torn arm,
after that, they
fulfill the pretense, like the railway people do. The
railway people have pretended to such a level that
you will feel that maybe they will not
die, they might die, who
knows, you see, for your total
security, the railway is making an announcement
that the Indian Railways wishes for your happiness and comfort.
You should try and
wish for it,
we both are on the same level.
Oh God, why are you saying this?
[Music] So,
I made such a common observation that
I noticed three ways that if there are
any of you who are fond of travelling, maybe
you can find yourself. One of these is those
people who go anywhere.  No matter what the
destination is, they travel by road. You go and travel
28, 2800 kilometers by road. I
mean, you understand that those people are
Ola drivers at heart.
No one is giving them an OTP.
Finish the TT ride and give it to them in cash.
No, you are not understanding, friends.
After driving 2000 kilometers, your mouth becomes
like a clutch. Whether you press your mouth or not, the
clutch keeps changing gears. Why do you have to
drive such a long vehicle? What is the problem for you?
If someone else in your life is
fond of driving such a long vehicle, I am saying, okay, if there is
someone who is an enthusiast, he should
drive. Drive a truck. Carry Kashmiri apples in the back. The
economy will benefit. You are going your
three ways. The heart wants it. I don't want it, friend. No, the heart doesn't
lose anything. Friends,
sit down. You guys are other types
of travelers, with whom I
relate a lot, people who like train travel.
Like me myself, I love train
travel because there are two or three things that
I like about it. One, you get to see so many people.
And passengers can also change,
unlike planes, there can be no change in the plane,
yes, I mean, if it has happened
[laughs]
then passengers keep changing, your
landscape keeps changing, sometimes something is coming,
sometimes something else is coming, okay, and I mean, the
network keeps coming, the best thing is that whatever
situation you are in, you can inform the world about
your situation because it is not like that scene where nothing is
coming at 400 feet, you know, I mean, it may come or it may not
come, your network will come after take-off or not,
it is not in your hands, it is in the
hands of how much we prayed that day,
and I mean, how should I tell you,
I like train travel very much, but I do
n't like its booking process, that
IRCTC has conducted a lucky draw, whether it is the
chosen one, whoever had kept it, what do I
mean, he had kept it for 16 Mondays, hey,
I have not got a husband since 16 Mondays, it is
leaving immediately,
I also do not understand their game,
sister-in-law, go around, go around, hey, if
you don't want to give it to me, then write abuses for the sister,
why will I wait, it may be, it may be,
I am Rohit Sharma's  I keep sitting like a wife, hoping that
my Tatkal ticket should be cleared, so the
process is challenging,
then again comes the third type
of traveller, who is not me, you are around me,
you might be around you, maybe you too,
who have seen this, you have seen their attitude,
see Bhaiya, we
like to reach every place before time, wherever we go,
we leave at 9:00 pm
because we think that going before time means being happy and living a happy
life, and these are the ghosts who get late
because all the time is
spent in [ __ ] knowledge, you are late, oh all this, come on,
sit down and leave, friend, you guys have not seen that,
see, we all, first of all, my friend Alpan, our
friendship has been going on for 15 years, 16 years, till now, I
like to go before time in a group, that is why I take SpiceJet, do
you like to go before time, I take
SpiceJet, those who
go before time take Indigo,
oh SpiceJet is something to be taken,
SpiceJet has installed ceiling fans in place of engines,
not even theirs, that Diwali
Diwali  It's clear that
their total plan is, let me tell you, SpiceJet's total
plan. Whoever
opened that airline, get more bastards. Their
total plan is to sell tickets, get passengers on board,
and then get a head count. If eight people
can fit in an Innova, take it by road.
They're saying, why bother the plane? The
patch is open at the top, and the
seats are attached with spit.
Brother, SpiceJet is a very light airline.
Friends, I'm telling you, are you
not a SpiceJet? You should take death,
don't take SpiceJet, because
why delay death for no reason?
Yamaraj has come to wait on a buffalo.
Brother, I'm not a chat guy,
but I have to tell you this.
I know, like I just
told you, it's been seven years since I completed stand-up, so of course I'm getting
shows. And one
thing I've noticed is that the clients are respecting me.
Like, finally getting their respect.
You can tell it in their eyes, you can tell that they
respect you, but there's
also a little problem that they're over-respecting me.
I'm telling you, there's a
lack of respect in all of our hearts.  There is a level when you start
getting more respect than that, then it increases. You did the
work in exchange for the respect you were getting.
What about in exchange for more? I am not guilty of all this.
No, who knows that he is fond of it. You don't know,
you don't know this, you come to
know about it later. Bhai
sahib, when you work, you must be doing it. Yes, then keep this in
mind that sometimes the client does
n't want just services,
not extras. Those who know, they know.
Leave it, friends, whoever you see, whoever is
watching the show for the first time, there is one thing Ravi
probably didn't tell you, I don't know, if you
people think that why are others laughing at this,
laugh and laugh, go to the
toll and get stuck in the jam, then understand
that wo
n't Ramra [ __ ] the
camera first. Let me tell you one thing,
this is not a part of the show right now. I am telling you otherwise.
Recently, I had uploaded a video. While
I was uploading it, she went to heaven for the
earth.
My sister, both of your Nar's children have troubled me so much, do you
understand? At 12:30 in the night, she called my manager
on his phone and said my  Delete the video
now his wife is lying which video should be deleted then
tell me completely I said you people don't watch the video till the end
so I have to
put important information here yes I
knew about your antics I am not a waiter I had
seen your antics so
friends the thing is that 8th March is the date
decided where there is a very beautiful moment in every comedian's journey on
which
he tapes his first stand up special
so I am taping that stand up special on
8th March in Gurgaon
I have written the ticket link here in the description and have
also put Samudra Pa, go and get those
tickets ok now just watch the video
and I am torn on him I don't even record
[praise] I do
n't go there you will get swept away you bastards
what were you saying I travel travel I have given them too much
respect like
for example these days
in the last two and half years wherever I am getting shows they are
calling me from Hawaii jazz
everywhere I mean I live in Delhi
shows in Chandigarh bastards  I am calling them from Hawaii Jazz, can
you see me brother,
please tell me, try
flying once, what do you mean, South Indian
beach people, look at them, they have
truth in their hearts, they have respect in their hearts, but
they are having fun, who flies to Chandigarh, friend, a
plane doesn't fly to Chandigarh,
Chandigarh, you see, they make them fly so high, but the
cars below are in a torn condition,
we are so inefficient, if anyone has gone by
plane to Chandigarh from Delhi, then there is no
person more despicable than you, that you
harassed any airline, you had
counted a good number of passengers in the Innova,
they did not, and before that, let me clarify one more thing,
if by chance someone has
not boarded a plane, let me clarify it for them, they are
calling me by plane to do shows, but they are
calling me only to places where there
is an airport, this is basic, there are
no scientific jokes at all in the show,
you can go by plane only to places
where there is an airport, basic means you
can go even to places where there is no airport, but
as a
You don't plan that surprise landing,
after you leave someone says it was written by them, oh
you should have told about it like this, oh you are having fun, you think,
you have a flight from Delhi to Jaipur, randomly
Bhilwara has arrived, it will be a disaster, you will not be a disaster,
forget it, the whole of Bhilwara will be a
disaster, oh brother the plane has landed, oh
where did the bus move, it did
not land, so this is this and I mean friend, see
how I am telling you this, recently
we actually went to Bhilwara to do a
show, if anyone from Rajasthan would
know, it is a very small town
district, the people there are very nice, it is a very
cute city and those people are very chill,
they are chill with cars and buses, they do
n't even need a green day because when so many people did
not come, they were saying they would come by road,
nine people would come in a Nova,
yes, if you spread a lap for one, they would come,
brother,
I got a chance to go to Bhilwara, so after a very long
time, the thing that I want to
share is that after almost 7 and a half years,
I sat in a train.  And the thing that I realized that day was that we were
traveling in planes for so long that there is a huge difference between the train and the plane
driver,
literally, I just told you basic jokes brother,
no, we did not know Christopher,
desi Aditi
Chopra, there is a huge difference between respect and
money, what about money, hat, that money, let me
tell you, yes the money is not there today, it is
not there tomorrow either,
they know, you are considering it yours, no, either there is a
difference in respect, like
I will give you an example,
you are getting so much respect in the train, it is only we people
who have started insulting the train,
we people who
look down upon the railways, that you are not understanding that
look at the railways, you go to any railway station of this country, even
where the train does not
stop,
there too they have written in big caps
on the board that the railways is your property,
what are you talking about
sister, I was 11 years old when I came to know about this
information, I ran away, I will give you the
papers,
you are not understanding, have I fallen into the hands of some wrong person?  I will do it
when their work is needed, they will leave. I got a
call. The entire railway is
sitting in despair. I tried to escape but did not
go. The papers kept in the hands of important people are
very good.
And I am telling you to see
how comfortable the railways are for you. To
help you, suppose someone among you has a
train at 7:30 am tomorrow morning. You
catch 74. They make
fun of you
and they don't even taunt you like this. They make you calm down. On the
contrary, they say to tell me, it's okay. It's
winter time. I can't wake up. It's
not comfortable. It's
15 minutes late. Tell me, you're crying. The
train is delayed by an hour and a half. How is the train delayed by an hour? My journey was for an hour.
I am two and a half hours late without even starting.
How can I explain this to anyone
or you? You are not understanding this. You must have
heard of this in India. You know, the
train starts from here. First
stop. The train is
delayed there. Hey, how did you do this Kirti? We had to leave
from here.
We would have gone ahead and got stuck in the Bhaam Bhaam. How come
[praise]?
I am telling them this.  Yes, I am
station master, listen to me, there is an engine standing there, bring the
engine, attach eight coaches and let's take it away, no
one will come to know, he is saying it through your ears,
you are not understanding, the driver sitting in the engine is
saying, Railways is my property, the whole
game is all about paper, brother, the whole game is all about
paper, there is comfort in Railways,
on the other hand, see, if you
take an air ticket, I don't understand,
friends, I have not travelled internationally,
so I am not telling you on that basis, I am
telling you about this country, what kind of
distrust is there in our country between me and the government that
they have to check my ticket outside the airport,
no, I have a problem with my mental balance
that I left the hustle and bustle
of the city and went to the airport at
5 in the morning in the
ravines, 25-30 kilometers away, without a ticket,
just to check that the plane is standing there,
I am a man of the earth, what is the
problem, why are you people not understanding that and I
mean, you go, I am saying, you people are
checking tickets outside, these airlines used to do it,
recently they have reduced it a bit.
You see, firstly I am not able to understand that air
travel has become so expensive, you are
charging 89000 for a ticket, even after that you are
not giving comfort, you people, in train travel, if
you go to drop someone without a ticket, you
think that the boarding is from Delhi, you go to
Gurgaon and lie down till
someone boards or gets off from Gurgaon,
friend, there is no comfort in airlines, on the contrary,
if any of us has a flight at 6 o'clock tomorrow morning,
you know, they call a day before from an
unknown number, from a number which is
not in any phone directory, saying
listen, come at 9 o'clock,
where do you come,
brother, I don't do all this,
I don't know where your air travel is, if it is not
for that, why does your mother
come at 3 o'clock, it is at 6 o'clock, the bastard is saying come at 3
o'clock, I will drop you,
casually, how are you talking, I will
leave it, I will drop you, aunt's aunt is
saying no, no, leave all that, tell me that
big bag in your bag  I took it which comes up to my
chest, I said yes absolutely I took it, he is saying
come at one o'clock, you are crazy, I had to take you to the
city,
why are you calling me so early,
he and I know the
biggest grief was that he said that I had
two techies, he said brother the plane has
flown,
your two techies are not letting you, don't mind
taking the dead body in the train, no
one is
saying I should take it
apple for
apple in the flight first, I am saying come on, the
security will be tight, it's okay,
you opened such an expensive card, the
security friend, you should see, the bastard is
outside me saying first show the ticket, okay I showed it,
go inside, they
check your ID on the booking pass, first you get your luggage, if you have put it in it, have you brought it, I will
tell you, you
see sister,
see what all have I put in,
or should I pick you up at 11:30 because of your father,
I have to give you the techie, if you have put it in, then they
check it there, then you go,
then the police check you, your
hand bags are scanned separately, then they make you
sit somewhere, then  You
sit for so many hours and then say come
birding birding birding then they check the birding pass
then when you are going on a flight or by
bus they check the ticket once again down there
after that when you
board the high-speed train you see sisters what kind of
behavior is this have
you seen the currency how many li's have you got so much
Gandhiji
on the other hand you will
not be surprised to know the day before yesterday my friend Arpan
dropped me to the engine in Aqua
and talked to the train driver brother the
boy is new
drive slowly only our trains are filled and
there those bastards I am saying come on you do
security do security but don't make fun of the
passengers you go they are saying first
you become Jesus I am not
listening to me oh you are you you have to be secular
crazy they are telling you to do one thing
take out the coins and keep them why take out the coins
say they are made of metal so what happens the
terrorists touch something in the metal
after that there is a boom should I
take it out he is saying why I said it is my
hard earned money
four one each
Sikh I said am I a beggar to you I
mean how are you talking so much
after taking 8000 from me
I am saying you are a good citizen
take out the coins no problem I took them out you are
saying take out the belt and keep it I
what about the belt the belt should also be made of metal not leather
some chemical is put inside the leather and that
too I said everything bu
and let me tell you I sincerely
want to help the country so much I do
n't have any problem I have so much
problem it
is dependent on the belt if I remove the belt the terrorist attacks that will happen after that are
just boom
they are not moving ahead of boom you are
not comfortable you are not comfortable from whom you are not able to be
comfortable and brother that will happen
you keep quiet for a while
when such good jokes are being played it is necessary to put your dirty ones
or I am lightening up so you
do it
okay I have set up such a good love studio
you have just got married it will be fine
[praise]
no you don't understand I am saying these
security at the airport are very Mashaallah  It is
tight, on the other hand, in the
name of security in the Railways, they are
pretending and let me tell you about this hypocrisy,
my personal thought is that this pretense has to be fulfilled always, the other person feels
hi, understand this meaning,
like the boys do
in relationships that girls think this is my
night and shining arm, this is this,
after that the arm comes off, torn
underwear, just like the railway people do, the
railway people have pretended to such a level
that you will feel that maybe they will not
die, who
knows, they might die, you see,
for your security, the Railways is making an announcement
that Indian Railways wishes you a comfortable and smooth
journey,
you just try and
wish for it,
we both are on the same level,
oh God, why are you saying that they should
not be protected, it does not matter, it must not have been written by them, let me
tell you,
they have kept the security protocol so strict in the railway station that no
one can break it, I
mean, you see, for railway security,
they have taken a wooden frame and called it
security, thinking
that it will do everything.  The scan is
happening, how your child is growing, everything is
visible,
so many divine machines have been installed, that divine machine in the
name of security makes a sound, beware,
Tutu,
my love, you should bear Tutu, you should
never go out, I have a real pistol and gunpowder,
SN Owner of
Railways, what is the joke, stay with me, don't lag behind,
SA Owner of Railways, so many times I took a real
pistol and gunpowder for testing, that was last
month in September, I had a
train from Nizamuddin Railway Station,
that damn wooden frame is broken,
understand, now it is not even doing Tutu,
I have come out with the bag, there is a
policeman in uniform behind me, brother, Tutu,
I want you to respect the duty at least, friend,
and like him, I said, they always keep the pretense,
you should see, when you go inside, they have
installed a baggage scanning machine in which
you feel that your baggage is being scanned,
it is not connected to electricity, on the
other side, the Railway Protection Force people are
pulling the strip with their hands
and because of completing the task, they have
a wire, such a thin wire, there
is a computer there.  It is installed in it,
you are thinking wow my luggage is being scanned, hey
go and see, the
policeman sitting in the computer is playing cards and
asking me which card in solitaire, hey
then open the cards and the passengers will be scanned, bastard, let
me tell you here, there is nothing
you should feel bad about, now we
all are a family in which some people are strange,
so let me tell you, I do not wish this
for anyone from my heart,
but you know, if terrorist attacks are
not happening at the railway station at
present because the terrorists are not enjoying it,
their challenge is over, they are
delivering bombs like Zepto,
no one is going to stop them and even after that, let
me tell you, if you still feel
that I am speaking ill of the Railways, I am
not speaking ill of them, I mean I am speaking ill of them,
you should not feel that
you people are wearing a cloak, let
me tell you how much difference there is between airlines,
airways, railways, in this plane, you would
know that if ever it happens to you that there is
less leg room because the planes are small, then
You say hey listen they
open their legs a little and say give me 2000 quickly
what happened friend that emergency exit sister
[ __ ] is saying emergency exit 2002 open it now open your
legs what a dirty deal it is these
in Thailand open for 800
and after that open your legs go on it is your
wish whoever you want you open your legs she is saying
then it is your responsibility I
said what responsibility are you saying open the gate
who is coming what is this
what kind of responsibility is this to pay money
if you do not know for
your kind information there is an emergency exit in railways too has
anyone seen it
today it is not visible because people are
taking entry from it
you should ever look you are lying on the side floor
three boys suddenly what happened brother what happened brother move aside
oh
you can come from the main gate it is a big different thing
but still still I will tell you
how much trust we have in railways you
listen this thing is very sweet very poetic
you should see this thing you should accept that you
travel in such lower berth  You are coming from far away, it is a
long train journey and your
train is delayed like this, normal
10-12
hours is normal, or when it is extraordinary
then 35-40 hours is
normal, what
happened, he is
going to me again, my brother-in-law left me, he must have his
own problems, he has gambled,
what do we care,
why should we think about everyone, he must have thought
that come tomorrow morning at 3:00,
where were we, yes, accept this usual delay,
you are travelling alone for 10-12 hours in the train, sitting on the lower berth,
in which bad time did you book the train, being so set
[laughs], I was
dying to taunt you, but
your seat on the upper side is in front  The
unknown passenger in the lower berth who doesn't even know you
just says this much, son, don't worry, we will
cover it at night,
you don't have self-belief, you will do it, yes,
Jai Ho, something different happens in your mind, don't
worry about your family, you tweet, we will do it
at night
[laughs]
Harry Potter came, what
happened, we don't understand, but
after two-three days you come to know in the newspaper that
eight people, three buffaloes are standing,
what is written below, it was written about them,
oh but comparison, comparison, let me tell you,
think on the other hand,
after boarding your flight, there is a delay of two hours,
but when your pilot came, he
said, dear, don't worry, we will cover it at night, it will
not break, brother, come here, come, come, we will
not cover anything,
brother, if you go to the road, your
sister will cover it, sister flies the plane,
keep it on the Nova of the spy Jat, we will travel on that,
otherwise we will cover it in the next, but
I had told you in the beginning also that at
night, this train  If
you have a train at 7:30, you catch 74. Try
not to cross-question anyone,
how will you do it? What is this? You can
catch people just for fun. You can pull the chain.
Railways is your property,
why are you not accepting it? You should have self-
belief from within. You are not understanding this.
Before we come to the train, I
want to tell you clearly,
tell them later, they will
not know. Avoid listening to half the words, do it in
reverse.
Then the tweet from Indian Railways is coming, we will
cover you at night. So, you have to keep
two things in mind, firstly, the
chain has an emergency brake,
friends, keep in mind, you guys are fine, it is a
responsible job, do not pull it casually or accidentally.
You should carefully see that firstly,
you have to pull the chain after seeing whether there is a station outside, did
you feel that there is a casualty or there is no cow's
udder
outside, because if you do not want to get down
and you mess up, then I will
tell you what the problem will be, the train
crosses the fields.  While doing this sometimes there are
sugarcane fields there now the trouble that you have
taken so the railways makes sure that you eat
sugarcane once
but their process of feeding sugarcane
is very different you come and then that come the
first thing you have to take care of it the second
thing you have to take care of is that this is an
emergency break there are some trains in
which food is available like
Shatabdi Rajdhani etc so if you are doing all this then
you should be very careful what people are
doing at that time because some carefree person is
eating Poha and the person sitting in front of him is
eating curd you were selfish you pulled the trigger
now be careful the person who is eating Poha is
eating curd from the person sitting in front
no do not spoil their mood
otherwise when sugarcane Ganeria is made and fed it is an even
tougher process then this and the
second thing this is also fine what about both of you
your cell phone company
both the mobile phones are of the
same PCO your son is having some
problem
you are standing outside you have to come
back
he has to go to Delhi
I will
leave it you have problem you have to leave
or you have to lose what all  What are you doing, listen, you
both settle it
[laughs]
both of you, what do you want to do,
go, is it
true, it's a rhetorical
question, people don't know, whenever this question is being
asked, the answer is
in the question, like you haven't seen, I'll
tell you, this is Amit ji's scam, have you
seen Amit ji's, as soon as you give the
correct answer, if the chair you are sitting on is the
correct answer, then lock the D, lock the D, lock the D,
brother, you must know,
friend, and if the answer is even slightly wrong, think about it, it's a
tough question, the
amount of money is huge, your father and sister
[Prashansa] have been stolen, you are coming, very
good, hey, or are you absconding, you have to go to Delhi on time, will
he be caught in the blockade, oh, you
should have told this too, so I was
calling you to tell you, but as casual as he
was in life, he is casual
about emergencies, friends, beware of such people because you might be considering
them as friends, listen, there's an emergency at my house, I'll
come after listening to three jokes, hey,
my blood pressure is rising, but now,
listen to me, my  Let me
understand once because how come you came with someone,
you are alone brother,
if I request you,
you can fill this chair, please, it's not a no no
thing, you understand, when we
upload the video, the public will be in
trouble, you think there is a bag,
what is there
in the bag, people are crazy, half an hour is left,
oh my god, where was the chain,
I will tell you the story of the chain,
look my friend, there is
a Shatabdi train from Delhi, Chandigarh
Shatabdi 740, listen carefully, the story,
Arpan, it's 737, the station hasn't arrived
yet, we both have to go to Chandigarh for the show,
his call comes, 737, Inder, I am late,
stop the train and hang up the phone,
hey, I have these powers,
my one touch, I am roaming down in the train with my laptop
bag, brother,
how can you stop the train,
what do you mean, there is no money in your bag, you are
talking nonsense,
friend, I got a call from him on 739, saying
Inder, and if you don't stop the train, then
pull the chain, what is your first plan
I was going to get cut like a buffalo by the train, there was a delay because
the buffalo is in
half and there were announcements going on too, dear
friends, did they have
any
meaning in what they had written, now listen to me, it was 740
and it was the day of the railways' surprise test,
what happens on this day, they would
leave the train on time,
hey, there were no sewing tests in school,
when the teacher came and said, oh now it's over,
that day the railways also did the same, the TT blew his horn and
showed everyone that the train has left,
my uncle is in the train, I have to go to
Chandigarh for a show, son, Arpan has
not come, and I am not able to understand,
just remember Arpan, pull the chain, aunty was leaving,
I said, chan,
you are not understanding, this is my daily work, this is
my daily work,
brother, you understand what I am saying, the train has left,
aunty has stopped, there is
strength in the chain, by the way, it
depends which one you pull, if
you pull this one, the life of the person stops in the throat,
but you are not understanding what
I have done with aunty, after all, I have to  I
realized that aunty was running away for some purpose,
you understand that when someone is running away, he has a
destination in his mind, I
immediately
showed the roof to the destination, I offered a sip of sips,
sat quietly, yes brother, thank you very much,
keeping the love of brother to brother, you
watched the video till the end, so as I promised
you in the previous video, we have
uploaded a new video and if you
look at it together, I have brought almost an hour of content in
front of you all
within a month and a quarter, now you have to
fulfill your responsibility friends, the message that I
gave you, you have to buy the tickets, on 8th
March it is a very special show,
I have made a show on my father, you all should
come and be a part of it, come with your family,
if you don't even live in Gurgaon, if you
know someone, please recommend them, there is a
ticket link in the description, there is a
ticket link in the first comment, and
we are coming to tour many more cities, come to the live show
so that we can tell you new content from
YouTube, but these are some of the things that
I have noticed, I think  I hope you
guys will try to understand these taunts that
I have made are some of my observations
which I feel that these things can be corrected,
many things have improved but these
things can also be corrected now, so if it happens then nothing
like it
and that's it, I mean you enjoy the video, it will be
written here like here, share here,
subscribe here, so you like, share and subscribe
and hugs and kisses as usual and we will
meet very soon with some other new video, for
now you keep sharing these videos in Pelam Pali
and enjoy, okay,
enjoy full fun, comment to comment see you very soon